DANIEL BABIN

519 Clover Park Crescent, Milton, ON · 905-699-3913 daniel.l.babin@gmail.com | https://danielbabin.me/portfolio/

Front-end Developer with 4+ years of experience, strong communication skills and a dedicated teamplayer. Has a passion for problem solving with code and strives to build a positive user experience.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2020

WEB DESIGN & INTERACTIVE MEDIA, HUMBER COLLEGE

FRONT END DEVELOPMENT & WEB DESIGN PROGRAM

2013 - 2015

INVESTIGATION – PUBLIC & PRIVATE, SHERIDAN COLLEGE

INVESTIGATOR AND SECURITY PROFESSIONAL PROGRAM

SKILLS

- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS & SASS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JQUERY
- GIT
- MYSQL
- AJAX
- RESTFUL API

- NODEJS
- EXPRESS
- NPM
- SOCKET.IO
- REACTJS
- BABEL & ES6+
- WEBPACK & PARCEL
- PHOTOSHOP
- ADOBE XD
- ILLUSTRATOR

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2016 - PRESENT

ASSET PROTECTION SPECIALIST, HOME DEPOT

- Reviewed CCTV Footage, identify theft and fraud patterns, and submitted detailed reports to police.
- Responsible for investigating External and Internal, thefts and frauds in nine stores within one District. Also responsible for teaching coworkers, communicating with store management and prioritizing my work loads.
- Active role in apprehending theft and fraud suspects while following company policies, maintaining a high level of professionalism and working as a team.

APRIL 2014 - NOVEMBER 2016

SALES ASSOCIATE, HOME DEPOT

- Responibilities: Created labels, stocked merchandise, ordered stock and managed daily responsibilities while helping customers.
- Provided excellent customer service and received an award for maintaining a high level of customer satisfaction. Persistant in understanding a customer's problem and in creating a solution.
- Learned how to use multiple store use applications which involved ordering items, setting up installations for appliances and selling to customers.

APRIL 2014 - NOVEMBER 2015

BANQUET SERVER, CLUBLINK

- Prepared the hall for events served guests and cleaned hall after events.
- Excellent team experience in a fast-paced workplace, had to coordinate with management and coworkers to complete tasks efficiently.